list-zilla.com 2011-02-15

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated: 1.25.2010

## Introduction

The following constitutes the entire agreement between you and Vendetta App, Inc. (List-Zilla.com), (hereinafter referred to as "LISTZILLA"), and sets forth the Privacy Policy under which all personal user information is governed by LISTZILLA. 

LISTZILLA takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using LISTZILLA. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information ("Data") that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by LISTZILLA, nor to persons that are not employees or agents of LISTZILLA, or that are not under LISTZILLA's control. Please take time to read this site's terms of use.

## 1\. Collection of Data

Registration of a member account on this site requires a user name that has not been used already, a valid email address, your first and last name, and an AlertPay account id (email address). You are not required to provide any other information if do not want to. Please be aware that the user name you choose, the e-mail address you provide and other information you provide may render you personally identifiable, and may possibly be displayed on LISTZILLA intentionally (depending on choices you make during the registration process, or on the way in which the site is configured) or unintentionally (such as, but not limited to, subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party). As on many web sites, LISTZILLA may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if it is LISTZILLA's policy to display advertising) is set forth below.

## 2\. Use of Data

Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your Data being made available to third parties unless provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates this policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by LISTZILLA to protect LISTZILLA's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on LISTZILLA to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.

## 3\. Cookies

Like many web sites, LISTZILLA sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on LISTZILLA and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties serving the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site.

## 4\. Minors

People aged eighteen (18) or younger are not allowed to become registered members of this site. For more information, please contact the administration.

## 5\. Editing or Deleting your Account Information

This site provides you with the ability to edit the information in your user account that you provided to during the registration process, by visiting your personal home configuration page. You may request deletion of your user account by contacting the administration. Content or other information that you may have provided, and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within site forums, may continue to remain on the site at LISTZILLA's discretion, even though your member account is deleted. Please see the site's Terms of Service for more information.

## 6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the site, and/or by a message being sent to the e-mail address you have provided, which is contained in your member settings.

## 7\. NO GUARANTEES

While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of Data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, LISTZILLA is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond LISTZILLA's control that may result in disclosure of Data. Consequently, LISTZILLA offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.

## 8\. Contact information

If you have any questions about this policy or LISTZILLA, please feel free to contact the administration.
